[applause]
but the people themselves are you,
I know some people are new
here and just for your clarification,
when we do this offering with our
hands, it represents our entire world. I knew the
infidels did it, then please
ask someone who knows to help them
with this. I remember how I first started
doing this and you worry, you study, it
represents the whole world, the world of a happy woman, calm down, the
films will be a plan, and
this is the fee for your class where you
are now, and Don John, I do not take any
money for training, we just need to
pay for the hand, for the hotel
tickets, we do not receive any payments for
these fees, for these keyboard training and
stuffiness, profit, but you need this
Aztec commandment, and this is the fee for this class, where in
this study,
you need to promise, and in my lesson, that
you will make this entire world of models,
Metabo, Metabo, Paradise,
Amitabha, video about us, this is your promise,
example, before the payment for
being in this class, the
whole world is represented as Raipo Metabo,
I offer this to you for this lesson, and at the
end of this lesson, on the ashes of Miguel
Continuing on the topic, pay for this, take it, you
understand well what a good
price is
[applause] these are
ember candles. At this retreat,
we are studying a wonderful great book. I love
books and I think this book is the
greatest book in the world for
you and it is called Lama.
Tell me, what does the path mean
for you to get these steps. A wonderful
book about how you can become, but if
you wear it and if you
listen very carefully,
try white.
You can become a bureau in reality. It
can give you water by studying in these
classes, but there are billions of
worlds and only people and it is cool. DotA is a cool thing. I
really love coder and you can
do it.
Spam would just follow these steps.
Okay, how are we going to do it? Arisha Ki. Sometimes
you have to pour T-shirts on me. What my
jeter told me and I studied this book
3 times.
I would like to finish all these things very
slowly and I thought that I have, as far as
webmoney goes, you know, we have been doing it for 9 years now and after
you are new today, I should now
grab you for this post and continue
studying well
[applause]
harmony, I think.  What else is this? It will take
about ten years. The next big
things affect more time. It doesn't
take so relax,
enjoy. It's a small problem. It
just comes with pain for
ten years. The next families, and I'm very
grateful to the people who bring their energy here. The axis of my lesson. We will work to teach the children of mothers and fathers. We have classes for mothers and fathers because I'm the same age as them. In the future, you are welcome
to bring your children here for this
class.
Your parents, grandparents, of
talking. A
survey after you become
grandparents yourself. You're still yours. Keep it up.
Well, so tonight,
between lunch,
this class is a little slow. I usually like to
stop after about an hour and a half
and finish because it's
hard to sit for two hours in class. I
love it, but within two hours, if I
give you a break, and about combo golf, but you're very
slow, come back, and we'll still have the same amount of
time to finish
this class. I
apologize. We have a two-
hour class in the evening. Try to drink more
water during the class and classes. It's
normal for me. Look, 1, 2, 3.  4 5 6
glasses of the East 3 in 1
please drink more fluids
during the lesson if you will if you
drink a lot of water during the lesson
we will also understand how you can
move faster and it's okay if you need to
get up, but because you
drink a lot of water and go out
take 2 where you
leave somewhere don't be shy just
do it and because we have a lot of
new people this time I thought 50
percent from 1 cm of the base and people I would
like to repeat a little the past
nine years of our classes I have three
ways how I do this I know that you have
heard about this before the next save is this
pen and the next four steps and skin in the
kitchen we will repeat these three things I will
definitely repeat of course many of
you have already heard many times about this hell but
I don't care
[music]
you understand the pen well and after
swimming in the pool
you will just fall and you will suddenly unexpectedly
break naked but if this is the
last thing you learned in this
life you will never again become you will not be
born in the animal world
you cannot become a dog it's
impossible  I constantly, constantly,
constantly repeat, and the pens are what
I mean by that, I forget about it, I just want to
protect you, listen carefully,
even if you've heard about this many, many
times, listen to how to teach, watch
me as I do it like a tape, I explain,
try to understand what I did, the next
step will say, and when you fly back
home, you will be sitting on the plane near
other people, someone will suddenly ask you,
what is your name, and you say, do you
know about the pen
[laughter], the
plane, if you sit, maybe
you won't recognize me by name, but you will
know about the pen, one hundred percent, just
imagine, on the plane or at work,
another person's day, other people, being born in the
next life of an animal,
just telling you about what I'm going to
tell you now about the old woman,
maybe this will be the best thing
that has done in my life, teaching, I
now think about what I will say
next, well, and then you will do it
without other people, try if you
really want to become all and
teachers, we have three trainings
every day, every year, one training
in Mexico in the summer, twice in America - the
Defoe Prize in
the fall and spring, I know, I know that Team will
soon begin teaching in
other places  For example, in China, I could be
strange, Russian, a country of
Russian-speaking countries, soon, I thought,
within the next two years, right,
and then you can become a teacher in
Asia, but everyone went, they wanted to
become this, probably everyone went, teaching
pens is a very ancient tradition and two
thousand years old, and the
standard of this ancient teaching is
when the teacher asks a question to
students and you give an answer, and we do it this
way,
and you jeans, but let's go, I gave this
explanation at British
Airways, and there were vice presidents of the
company, I had them with me, they were
somewhere outside the city, and I split them about this for
two days, the first thing was,
you still have pens, and I said, but listen, I
will tell you, ask questions, you
please answer me, and let me
tell you what this is, and all these nine
vice presidents of the company, they have answers, and
I said, what is this, please, and the
British vice presidents, okay,
give me good ones, what is this, don't
touch the one sitting in front, those sitting in the
back, I want you to answer,
please, I will give money for
this later, okay, but if the people in the back don't
answer, I won't go back, okay, what is this
Began, look, here's a little dog
running into the room
[music]
and I'm showing this dog and what the dog will do,
rolls up to show a question, a
question arises, an important question, part 2,
the dog looks at this pen, of course, she
looks, but does she see the pen, but she doesn't
see, and what does she see, something that can be
chewed, Nevsky's prey,
who is right, at home, a dog or a person, both are
right, big, and why do they have a game,
and from a website, they can write, no problem, it's
great, payment for both are right, now
listen to YouTube, you came to me,
and on the very first night you learned that many
people didn't know for 2,000 years, Boriska,
and that such a thing is just like that, it's very important
with evil, gambeson
[music]
what is emptiness now, I leave this thing
for 100 lire, and the garden, what's
next, what's next, yes, everyone leaves,
all the dogs leave, and people leave the
room, everything is empty in the room, at that very
moment, this pen or this toy
for the dog, what is it, she gave a wonderful
answer, this is what we really
call emptiness, no
one hears, this is a toy or  The pen
she says this is the real thing, just a
product,
why am I glad that this is exactly what
my teacher didn't say, you'll go, they're
bright, and you'll start, and I said, what's the
problem with business, emptiness, and since I'm going to
use this, opening a business, and he did
n't say, I'll take you, and after a
while, it became one of the
largest jewelry companies in
the world, Warren Buffett bought this company in
2009, and the newspapers in New York wrote, "
How did you do it?", "How are you there?" I was burning,
emptiness,
let me tell you what simplicity is, it's not
three, and put down the right people
[music]
who will never be able to make a
company that Warren Buffett will buy
later, between the request and 1, here's
the area,
what is simplicity? Close your eyes
[music]
Cross your legs, what is wise? Close your
eyes,
blackness, blackness, blackness, this won't help
you. If you understand the slope, then you
can. The company itself is a group of
companies in the world, not a problem. Good. 2. The
next idea for the articles
[music]
Don't think about anything here, if  Any
thought comes to your consciousness,
let go like clouds that fly by. It won't
help. It really won't help
you. What kind of food will this be? Consider sitting
for an hour, being repaired all day long
and not thinking. Fat, a new dance in the world. Here's a whole
new dance in the world.
Look, hello, I
want to show you something on my phone. I
left this ID card. The whole world can watch. Like this,
everyone's dancing like this. Who's dancing?
Where's my phone? Where's my phone?
If you meditate in this way
and leave and the understanding that you
don't think about anything, then definitely sow the seeds so that
you lose your phones every
day. This is interesting. Raven, BAFTA no. 3.
What's the idea? Point your feet. Sorry.
[music]
But there's nothing good, nothing bad.
Stay neutral. If someone
kisses themselves at home, smile.
[music]
If you hate someone, do
n't get angry. There's no cult, nothing good, nothing
bad. About Yubico,
even after you get it, we will have to
remain neither happy nor
sad forever. Have
you ever seen these
beautiful images?  then everyone was
smiling because I was good there would be
happiness inside Fabia
this is the idea just watch the measure don't be
happy they won't be sad it won't
help you then this is when the pen is
here on the chair
ok
and all the people came out all the dogs came out it
stays while there is emptiness and Geshe Michael
comes back hello they were standing what's new
and when I come up now at this
moment it is not something empty.
and when I go in, here I am, approaching,
nothing, still approaching, nothing, when I
looked down at you, nothing becomes
something, emptiness becomes a pen, and
why do I have a seed in my consciousness, it’s
clear, and this seed opens
when it
could not be open,
people, not open, people, not open, not open, not
open, it opens, and then a
picture pops out of your consciousness, and
the picture
wraps this thing, and this thing
becomes a pen, a very small
picture with pens comes out of your
consciousness,
why can’t I see yet these pictures exit
my consciousness, and the pen becomes a
pen, all my life I can’t
see this because it’s too fast,
65 per second, like that, very fast,
like in the video,
if the hotel has very bad
internet, and you watch a movie, most
movies are shown at 24
frames per second, you, 65 seconds, I sewed,
why are there so many movies? Because in a movie
you use only your hearing and that’s all, and you have a sense of smell, you have a sense of touch,
sensations, you must have the
best internet plan, 65 seconds per
second, you can’t see. If you
meditate every day, one day
you will see, this somehow happens.  I've been waiting for
this for two days, why because you'll
call or write messages, I know that's
right, but you'll see this experience
directly,
you'll meditate every day, so
I'm here yet, it hasn't opened up, it hasn't opened up, it hasn't opened up, it hasn't opened up, it has opened up, and the
seed is opening up, and I suddenly
see a pen,
now I have another one,
offer yourself this,
children love it, it's not opened up, it's not opened up, it has
opened up, the house has opened up, you
see, depending on what kind of seed
you have, consciousness itself doesn't
become something,
now the question is, you guys, tell me, is
this a pen, does it come from a pen, or does it
come from me, where from here
or from here to she says, the
pen comes from you, very well.
comes from me now listen if
one thing comes from you your
seed it means that everything comes from
you well your power our children
your work your city
your country even this conversation
that you will see now if you don’t
like it.  Velov, I say, don't forget, it
comes from you
[music],
and if you like my lecture, everything
comes from you twice. If you plant a
seed, then there was no experience in
building a business.
I spent thirty years debating and chance, I
knew nothing about business, nothing, and then my
teacher once said, "You'll go to Mejor
and start a business park." Shut up, you'll
go to the authorities, and then he said, "
Why do I want you to try
planting seeds?" The measures will be your
laboratory, and then you'll actually
see how everything comes from within.
You'll plant the seed for a wonderful business,
and then you'll see what happens. They carried this, I'm
teaching you correctly. Then you
can make the most wonderful company
in the world. It's clear it will
work. But if it worked for me,
you can use it too. It
uses it. You just have to understand how to
plant seeds. By the way, it took us
9 years in a row. We're done with this. We need
many new people today, and that's only
because new people are here.
Tomorrow, I'll destroy you with new
ideas,
and today,  Just a memory over the
last 9 years that we have been
through, I teach you everything in your
life, it's all the same as a pen
comes from at least master it from you if if
you have good seeds, study
how to plant and you can have everything you
want one woman told me one
woman told me I was walking can I
use four steps
to plant a seed for my husband
of course she says but if what you
say is true then I will plant 7 for
men then I will go home I will lock the
door and if my husband comes from
me he will come to my in we are in my
apartment and I tell him try and
then yes I planted a seed for my husband and she
went to buy groceries in the store
returned to her apartment locked the door
if yours comes from me he
will find a way when brother earth me
correctly and she began to wait one day
nothing happened in the name of nothing
happens
3 day a
plump man who delivers
sex affairs knocked on the door opens for
and they all got married
just plant the seed and don't worry
without a family with
seeds for me nothing is impossible you
all  can you reach the hanger well how to
plant seeds how to plant it on
forst four steps
[music]
I was supposed to use
100 dollars but jasmine gave me more
if I don't spend I'll be stupid let's do
this 400 dollars the camera
can follow me they're fiddling with me
now I'll go ok this can
reach let's go see
[music]
[applause]
come on come on let's start look here
ask the cameras now please don't
get up
then everyone will be able to see well just
people who can't appear with cameras
I have advice for you
take out your phones and
record this is probably the most important video of
your life you can take a video well
where are your phones take out by the way
if you are far away you
can record from the screen it's the same
guy there don't have and don't
post these entered you chat because
I will have problems then please I
beg you only for you for your
families for your friends don't try this
post this video 2-3 minutes for
tomorrow morning
Please, please, please when
you eat
breakfast to a wonderful man again
next day 2 day
look at this wonderful man
again me 3 look at the video and this
wonderful and just from just a postman
you will use and more successful
you will have tasteless feet this is
enough you can
cool in this you understand
health energy
four steps you need to decide what you
want all the time I will send my
children to study the best university
you want a wonderful family you want
your mouse to wash the dishes
study the four steps use them and he
understand or me next week I will
be 67 already
I do ballet of course usually
retire sick pain runes send at 27
years old
and inside you will be happy
super happy bolts the most important thing you can
share this with others you
can make this world happy
you can be spiderman
superwoman super woman you can
do this if you use 4
step 1 you decide what you want teams
that held you want this evening
he wants 4 and he wants to invest this
money for 400 dollars next week
I want me  there were 4 thousand
dollars but tonight this is not
a demonstration this is subtly Geshe Michael
creates his own money I plant
seeds with four 400 dollars
because I want to have 4000 and so my goal you
cannot plant a seed without another
person can you play basketball
without having a floor
what is karma floor for basketball the
second ball you need to find a person
with whom you will plant a seed and this
person this product he must want the same thing you
want and you
let's share what is your name and
thus I will ask
the bath a very very serious question do you
want to have 400 dollars now just like that for nothing
she asked so surprised
raise her hand she needs help 1 2 3 I
[music]
to understand karma you need to see
it yourself do what you say what
think about what you need to see
yourself
one two three and this picture when
the hand opened this picture it
gets through the window of my eye and
this picture she touches this and
this perch even though mom
touches in my
consciousness creates an imprint in my consciousness
of youtube after  Two hours creating a seed in
my subconscious and I see typos at first,
after two hours the
seed becomes with my consciousness and this is good
news, you want bad news, it will take the
toilet before the server disappears 4
thousand dollars I told my teacher
Sasha K I'm American I like the
next life I want now and we
said McDonald's if you work at
McDonald's and ask him to make French fries
and fries and you
set a timer and if it takes
more than 2 minutes understand and I told
my teachers I
love sushi I love you but I'm
American we created fast food
I'm not going to wait for the next life
to get 4 thousand 4000 I
want now
he says about
next week then you need step
number 44 then stage flight seed with water and
they will open quickly you know a lot of people
they help other people company like
Warren Buffett why don't they know how
to plant how to water
how it is he has and will create his 4 thousand
dollars next week very easily let's
go can you answer me  how he will do it
became a cafe cafe meditation she earned
her 400 dollars she for soot this
evening when I went to raise my room
and put my head on the pillow and the
last thing you will think
before you go to the network
that think from which you fall asleep it
will stew in your mind all night
this is very important you do not need to think about your
problems when you go to bed we
can when you go to bed just about
your problems and survey sew but
when you sleep do not go to sleep like this
on me my children are not studying they will not be
able to get into university I do not have
enough money if you think like this for a
year when you go to bed when
these worries all night boo is going on in
your head it is very important when your head
hits the pillow think about the good seeds
that you sowed today during the day do
not think about anything else and then
tonight I handed over thousands of dollars
in one night I gave her 400 dollars and
she was so happy and so happy and
she and then you can fall asleep
you transfer 1 result
and fall asleep think about your good ones
with this you can not fall asleep  Fall asleep, think about
your problems, think about your problems tomorrow,
when in the dark of the night, the problems of the night
become bigger and bigger,
think about your problems before breakfast,
make yourself a good breakfast, start
eating and let's
now think about my problem
and then your problem is very
small, a good breakfast,
wonderful sunlight and your
problems will automatically become smaller, do
you want to think about your problems,
please do this over breakfast
at night, in the evening when you start to go to
bed, this is a very bad thing and a
very bad time to think about problems,
why because you are tired and it's
already dark around
and the problems at this time begin to
increase and become bigger,
promise good coffee, meditation, hands,
then you start to sleep, let's talk about
good problems, good things all your
life,
promise please good about Geralt,
these are four steps
every evening, thank you, that's
enough video now, don't forget
tomorrow you will need to review his
schedule and the next day and the next
day, then you begin
to achieve success, after that there will be a
part with you, one-one, and I will be needed, I
understand this is not about me, I
will try for the program that we
organize here, this is for you, all you, you are interfering with
using the four steps, you become
successful you begin to share the four
steps with others
all is well the struggle and my goal for
this evening is to teach you three
three things first.   The
second thing is four steps, you'll find out, here's his
9 years of work, do it in one evening,
imagine her so happy,
I'm really lucky. The third important thing is
four steps,
now the level is two husbands in the kitchen,
level 2 increases, you're in the kitchen, if
you remember all these three things, a pen, four
steps, and two husbands in the kitchen, nine years of
work for you, and it's closed by you. I
need two husbands than Jamie.
2 are the most wonderful. Dinner and these guys,
let's sing, and more water or liquid in
any
way, let's, on the other hand, only
guys, okay, such two wonderful,
handsome guys,
let's thank Tim, he's president &
CEO,
and Jamie started the Dynafleet Bass project.
[music]
[applause]
5,000 videos are freely available,
free online lesson, Jimmy,
because you can do this. Jamie, thank him. In
fact, a lot of videos are posted in
Chinese.
I just suggest you be sure to
watch them there. Don't forget, during
breakfast, I'll think about my problems.
No, after breakfast, 5,000 videos are posted
on the site,
watch at least one. You're going to work.
Just listen at least and then you
will be happy well we will do two
husbands here is such a story the one who years ago
all the work in the family
was perfectly calculated the male
responsibility is about work to make
money well but the female responsibility is to
take care of the children from cooking to buying
groceries a hat a hundred-year-old system the old one
that we had now here is now a
good new system the wife's job is to
take care of the children cook to buy
groceries and earn money and the husband is
free to watch TV a
good job I like it this is very
wonderful for the husband a mustache a
new system let's say for example I am
such an
ordinary housewife I work every
day and in the morning I need to take the
children to school I work all day very
tired by the evening after work I
need to go to the store to buy
groceries to pick up the children from school
to return home to cook again
absolutely tired and exhausted it's
hard and so let's say I'm just a
housewife
I work all day well let's say on Thursday
I worked all day
and I leave will work to
pick up my children from school and then the boss runs up to me they
say are you home leaving but don't
forget that tomorrow tomorrow morning is
special we have an online conversation we have
all all international offices  There will be
calls and you have to come to work an hour early,
of course, don't come at 9, you
have to be there by 8, listen to me, do you
understand, and what does that mean? Do you understand? If you're late,
I'll fire you? I understand, that
means if you're late, I'll fire you. I
understand. Yes, and Mom is going home. It's very
important to meet your children.
Here, you guys will be my children.
Come out as my children, guys. These are my two
girls. And of course, I have to tell them
about the new plan.
See you tomorrow. Listen, guys. Mommy's office. He'll
just fire me if I don't do everything on time.
Tomorrow, please, get
everything ready an hour earlier, not by nine or
eight,
please. And he didn't ask Putin. An hour
earlier. He said if I don't come, I'll
fire him. Well, tomorrow
we'll go to school an hour early. You
need to help Mom. Please, please, get dressed. Please, put your
shoes on already. So, have all your homework
ready and be ready to go.
7 o'clock. Okay, such wonderful children this
year. I'm so proud of you. I'm having the most
wonderful day. The next morning, at 7
o'clock in the morning, the door opens.  What
are you doing, what's the solution, got dressed, you're not
even wearing shoes, a foot, and you're still in your pajamas, that's what
mom's going to fire, stupid, dumb kids in
major
[music]
why are these guys? Because they
heard mom and said bad words. Did
anyone else hear mom's bad
words? You, who heard mom? Look,
you're the dumbest kids. In mom's mind,
after two hours it's not enough. She just
planted a lot of seeds, a lot of bad ones.
Then we go to school. She runs to work, a
little late, told the boss that there was
terrible traffic, that there was a traffic jam. Everything seems fine.
Next week, she comes home. It's
Tuesday. I went shopping while I sang. I
took the kids from
school. She comes home absolutely tired
and goes to talk to her friends.
I'm so tired of this job. I
bought groceries, picked up these kids from
school, such a difficult life. I still have to
make dinner. But one good thing
my life gives, gives, and hugs are
the best in the world. He's the best
hugger in the world. Let me show you
how we walk along the road, and at home I'm ready. You're
stupid, like him.  Called me a fool I didn't
do anything I didn't say anything I
then that door you're a fool turned me into a fool
I didn't take anything is it true is it a
teaser true she didn't take anything yes
she yelled at her kids last week
she put them in jail 7
now give me a good answer from SAS and
go I also have jet lag I came
home again muzzle I didn't do anything it
just meant me yelling I didn't do anything
you did something what do you
look last week darling
I'm at home paper opens open with you opens look look look
darling I'm at home you're a fool just like a pen it
comes from changing although you understand it comes
from me the whole problem is my problem it's my
fault now I'm very surprised by you guys it's
very strange but the pains are different no one
asked me I was in a hurry why do you have
two husbands no
one asked at all to the soldiers what do you have with
me ask why do you have two husbands it turned out come on come on
let me
explain now this first one will go
why do I have two husbands this one maybe it
comes from me comes from mine just like a
pen
we can call Mr. Pen here  this one, this one, it
comes from me, this one,
can
I give you instead of pens and a star pen,
and this one, and this one,
his name is as soon as I
opened the door, how long have you been saying that in
your life, this one, this one, Mr. I have
n't done anything about the rhythm,
and this one, Mr. pen, I now have an
important question, and are you ready, one of these
husbands actually exists, one of
these husbands doesn't exist, can't
exist.   does
it exist or not yes it exists this one is
real this one comes from
me but this one doesn't exist this one doesn't
exist you see this one does
n't come from seeds this one is
not what is called a pen this one is
impossible to have such a thing why
because everything comes from itself
everything comes from seeds if one thing
comes from seeds
then everything comes from seeds you see this one this one doesn't exist
but this one this one is
real it comes like a pen
from a mineral
now a big big big question
[music]
when you get very angry
in the kitchen in the kitchen at which husband are you
angry at this one why do you hear you
can't be angry at this one why become an it
comes from you you created it of course
you can't be angry at it if you
understand that it comes from you you can't
just get angry that's your
problem you see no need to be angry about
nothing he didn't take off he's the most ordinary typical
walrus we can say he didn't
do anything it doesn't matter to me I understand of course I can't get
angry at him but this one
now look if you at this
Focus husband darling I'm home
you're a fool that's when I look at this I'm not a
fool I don't understand fool next question
when your husband how to prove that he
really rules that you're
really stupid I looked look
ready I'm home you're a fool I'm not a fool you're a fool that's it
you just proved
that you are then that you are a fool so that a
real fool you just proved it
why because you gave it to him now what will
happen next week with me
look again
if I'm not a fool you're a fool hi guys
mommy at home hi how are you how are you
doing
dopamine they fight
why because I have bad seed
woman
who planted this bad walls in consciousness
I planted and when in the kitchen let's all go back again
you are the stupidest
stupid children in Guangzhou
didn't give
you a fool you're a fool you're the
stupidest children in Lojer
darling you're a fool
support fool stupid children hooray
stupid children and such a wheel of life  and God is
constantly Alice life is clear okay we
spend our whole lives like this you
got angry at your husband you're a fool they put you in jail for 7
and the
next week the children are behaving again God this is the
wheel of life
samsara who creates this you did
why now it's
very important everything that I taught the
last 9 years I will tell you you in
five minutes and I will tell you the two most
important things in the world
set first Ingo good goes to the
and the handle on it has a mustache they are brothers you
can use your phone and his
handle pruhi emptiness feed emptiness there is
never karma without emptiness and two
sides of the same phone
they always go together where is karma in
this family in the kitchen where it
spins like this here it is all the time feed cow
return and karma karma and now for 100
dollars
[music]
where is the emptiness in the kitchen where is the simplicity in the
kitchen where is the emptiness of the kitchen
Joe asked
I sat in the kitchen I wanted an answer not a
question I would ask him I just
helped him make a translation where I
put Jamie's compartment to be wet
what is emptiness and what is karma
who by  Starukhin Jamie post so m and
why is he not there, he doesn't exist, he didn't
take anything off, there is no such thing, it can be hinted at in
any kitchen of the world which
says he didn't do anything, he is
not real, he doesn't exist,
he doesn't exist in the kitchen, the bank is empty, he is emptiness in
the kitchen, emptiness means
this emptiness means that it is the husband who is
not your problem, he does not exist, he does
n't even exist, you can call
him, he did nothing, you can also
call him power, it is called the block, the
emptiness of the husband, this one is impossible, it is
impossible,
every
single thing that your husband does, he
comes from you, everything your husband
says, everything your husband does comes
from the feed, prove that you don't understand
Buddhism, call him a fool,
call him hydrogen, this means that you
really don't understand anything
about Buddhism, you don't understand, okay,
ready for another 100 dollar question, thanks
for the money, mommy, mommy, thank you
[music]
okay, question, here's the question, next
question, and he's feed,
what is the best thing to do when
I come to the kitchen,
nirvana, nirvana in the kitchen, what
is nirvana  in the kitchen in the kitchen here's a
good question nirvana
in the kitchen became plumes shut your mouth
100 dollars what is nirvana expensive
and I'm home you're a fool
and I'm tired I'm tired of this wheel
life is so makes me feel tired all the time
let's stop this
[music]
in a year or it's clear this is nirvana
if you can't control yourself
go to the toilet if you need to yell
go to the toilet open the door
look in the mirror and yell there you're a
fool understand and that will be right
that will be right this is called
nirvana some people told me I
lived why do you constantly tell these
funny stories why do you
always talk about the kitchen and
about children in fact you need to teach
August we came drills to Bali drying
your story we need to dry on a according to the
article in fact it all happens
from the kitchen it starts it's clear this is not
done in order to be in
temples or some temples to be at
teachings emptiness
it was created in order to use
it in the kitchen you need to use this
understanding according to the article on  You don't
need to go to the temple in the kitchen and study emptiness there.
Everyone can go to the temple and study it.
Toyota won't help. Your laughter won't help.
Use the understanding of fasting. You're in the kitchen. There's nothing
in this
understanding that you can apply to
your kitchen. There's nothing in the kitchen that
you wouldn't find in the understanding of emptiness.
This was all created to make
you happy, and you need to
use it at your levels.
We understand. Peter, thank you. Good husbands. This is
nine years of repetition of material for 9 years.
We've been going through this. Drink
something, but bring water to
drink and more. Your brains need
water, and darma
needs brains, so darma isn't needed.
Water is needed. Now we're ready to start. The next
hour is empty. Half an hour, right. We should finish by 3 o'clock. Let's
go. After 9 years of
studying, we've achieved the point where we
realize that just like cliches,
no one says I didn't do anything.
One-two-three cliches. A
cliche means in Sanskrit. It means
this when you're very angry. When
you're upset. Mental presentation.
When you're upset. It means on the beach
now in Perm. Ancient ancient books.  A
very famous book from the Buddhist two thousand years
brings this book I am
selecting young translators because
in order to translate these books you
will need 27 years we have a plan 27
years but only three years closed he will
finish this book in 2026 his hair
will look like mine
in a nursing home and we will finish this
book really we are working on it
2046 he will want 4 parts the whole world the whole
universe
all the stars of the planet
this whole world all people come from
means karma means from a combination
means the whole universe comes from its
karma and then what does it mean in the market valley
dog
food three types bytes first but
raw karma is the main form of food
the mind thinks and what you think in your
consciousness is raw food
now it moves your mouth and moves
your hands New York
when you scream at your days oaks
glues these stupid children the stupidest children
why am I saying this that moment before that
I thought these children should have been
ready I don't know why they parts mouth I
talk in my own mind and
after that the stupidest  stupid children, you
see,
comfort for enemies, that is, the karma of consciousness goes to
pirates,
then opens your mouth and then pushes
your column.
Three types of karma were the first thinking
agency, what do you think, these are hormones,
just thinking, in short,
I thought consciousness itself, I refused to
be ready for my children, and now they are
fighting, I am so tired, but this is what I
think, it pushes my mouth to open, the
stupidest day, you see, that's how three
types of karma are: 1. What to think about, a new background, a
moment before something plays out,
stupid children, and then he yelled. Look,
stupid children, and deep into the house, first it makes you
open your mouth, you see,
dead, and these three
[music]
think about, talk, and wave your
hands, what do they create, these seeds, these
seeds,
what 7 do they create, rain, and now I just
told you, she is in the kitchen,
and the whole kitchen is empty, you see, deception,
if you get upset or angry in
your consciousness, then your mouth opens. The
stupidest children, and then what happens?
Someone tell me if I yelled at
my children, what happens then, what will
happen to me in the kitchen.
[music]
yours, yours, can call them, yours, can call
you a fool, I'll give the money to your mom,
okay, it's for a collage, collect money for
your child, put money on a stick, your
child has now earned money for a coach, you
understand, mom will give you this
money back when you're cold, study
well, I planted a seed, I
speak well now in the kitchen, my powerful one
calls me a fool, and when I get angry,
now a question for you, if I understand about the
seeds,
will I be
angry at my husband because and perhaps
because the power called me roads, if
you are a good Buddhist, and as long as you
use emptiness in the most difficult
moments of your life, not in temples,
it's very easy to sit in temples and just
read the knowledge of emptiness, this is not because I
will create an understanding of the knowledge of emptiness,
he created the knowledge in the article so that
you can use it in your kitchen,
use it and on your roots, it's clear I'm at
home, you're a fool, it's clear and don't upset
who created this husband, you created, you
created him, you can't, you can't
blame the pen on everything, like a pen, it
comes from you, calm down, calm down and
You need to call him dear, just
start creating this cycle all your
life. You know people like Kutya, about
whom I
accidentally have children. The next day, you can
yell at you, you yell at your husband
again, the children quarrel, swear at the
children again at the rally and again you have to yell at you
and this is a huge, huge cycle:
you yell at your husband, you go to work, your
boss yelled at you, then created such a
boss who yells at you, you did it
now. I find it very funny to you. I'll tell you
something. You understand now how to be a
good Buddhist and now in Odessa, you
can achieve nirvana. It doesn't mean anything.
No one can make you into a left
world, this is nirvana, Geshil, and I'm
so happy I arrived in Bali on the
first night, Sergeant told me in contrast, and
I just went into the kitchen and my husband
called her a fool, I just had to
remember who planted this seed, now
today we will give you a truly
real understanding of emptiness, it's
called Jamie, really, the wheels of
life
are called, he shouted and children can be frames, she yelled at the
children, my husband yelled at me, she
yelled, maybe the children are terrible, terrible children, she
yelled, you can
scream loudly, screamed children are terrible, we have
already studied, then you all Buddhism today and
Sasha, whether you are how can we even
finish it, people go home, I need to
spend my life here,
but if you meet yours, maybe
tonight in a hotel room, he will
say, darling, you really are such a
fool,
you will forget to
sit down, free in 1 second, especially, and
the blessing of a wonderful explanation of
Buddhism, and tonight something will
happen, someone will definitely take,
calls you a fool, you will have
some problems with someone, a
problem with  someone and you will forget everything that
I told you today rapport and
despite this we need to repeat
this six or seven rubles and again and again
and again this is for nothing we cannot
remember one race at a time lay down on the
bottom and a one-time lecture
if yours is possible calling you fool
tonight all my Buddhism will dissolve
but despite this you study study and
study
keep coming keep coming keep coming
you
chose that wedding now we are ready to
start the next chapter and I am going to
use simplicity
well disassembly hump
there is one book and there is a picture on the
page you have from the manual 1 view hand with a
ball and there is such and there and there is an
A6 sheet of things we are ready to start the class we are
ready to do tonight tomorrow
morning we will do three hours of
study we will start with meditation and we will
take a short break and we will
really study for three hours your
butt will get tired but your consciousness your brain
will move well
three hours very difficult for you very
difficult for me but we will study and it
will be difficult a little
we will study and what is this beach
when you have  I'm upset,
angry, and calling my husband in my kitchen,
who called you a fool. I have
n't done anything. I call him every day, every
day, between. I don't know why there are
two sufferings in life. One
suffering is a bad husband, bad children.
This is the first suffering. What is the second
suffering? I don't know why when we
met, my husband was so wonderful, he
always gave me flowers. He always filled me up. darling,
but now he doesn't call me a fool.
In the beginning, my children were so wonderful,
although they didn't quarrel all the time. It's clear.
These are the two types of suffering. One is
quarreling children, the other is arguing husband. The second is I
don't give in. Why
was he so wonderful before, and after all, they
were so peace-loving? Both
sufferings must be stopped. Okay, now
when you get upset in your kitchen, and even
if
you heard this lecture today, you
have six reasons. Wonder
why you'll get upset again.
Well, here's this one,
pepper it here, let's
talk about it. One is why you're upset
with your husband because you're offended by
your children. When you're offended by
your children, you planted a mustache in two different
families.  1. I first planted the seed screamingly,
the second because you got angry,
upset with your children, planted a
bad habit,
2. 2 things you planted
your can blah blah-bah-bah-bah and you
planted a bad habit, you will be
constantly angry, angry
at the children, yelled at us, two
types of seeds planted, 1. Your husband will
yell at you, and the second,
you will be constantly
angry, in
the kitchen, at work, wherever you
are, the first reason is a cliche, the first
reason for anger is before, before, as the anger
which you created, you get
angry every time, you did this many, many times,
you, as a person who constantly
drinks a
lot of alcohol, you simply become
attached to anger and minced meat and the old
anger creates new seeds for anger, you
edema, those people who are addicted to alcohol,
you have addictions to anger, this is the first,
well, how to stop your anger,
stop his anger, I asked again
how to stop your anger, stop, let's take it,
I was going, it's stupid, stop, let's take it,
stop your anger, but  this is the truth
if you try to
yell and controller at your children you will
plant the seed of control yourself and
when you come to the kitchen this
good seed will open you understand and so
where when you are going to yell at
your children I have very good
advice for you wait 10 seconds
count to 10 look now I
will show you kids it's time for
school and those I wanted to say you are so
stupid 1 2 3
[music]
five six seven eight nine the
stupidest children and you said you are the stupidest
children well just hold for 10 seconds
every time you want to yell at
children you
understand you are stupid I'm not stupid you are a fool
just wait 10 seconds for the
next ten seconds this is a very
strong useful pocket more useful and
well wasn't it
you who said don't yell at your
husband I didn't say this because you can't help but
do this you understand you can't
help but do this I just said what I
said wait 10 seconds and then
yell at him and karma karma of these 10
seconds it is incredible  strong is much
stronger
they told you hanged don't say bad
words no I said try continue
say very bad words to your husband
very wonderful but wait 10 seconds
understand and plant a good seed and it
will be stronger
aroma understand and you will develop a habit
you will develop a habit stop the
second thing I have here wait
first your just wait 10 seconds
control you have an alcohol
addiction I don't have an alcohol
addiction problem Norika knows Joyce
knows I have kidney problems I do
n't have a problem with alcohol but I
like something in secret give me this
but if I have here you know more
a little watermelon and if they don't give me a
donut I went fight so 10 seconds water
and that's it 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 and there is good here
any bad habit addiction
just hold here and seconds
wait or the second thing on the sheet
that you have stolen the second advice
that is there is called
intimacy but don't allow
and  donut get close to your body
tell Joyce
tell Noriki don't let them bring
donuts into the room came in why
actually and I was walking can't control
himself you know so if you put
donuts in the room came in he will just
eat everything he didn't know how can't
control himself this is the second advice on
how to continue to do for anger
good just don't do it
avoid darling I'm at home from stupid
and I forgot and I forgot forgot now
wait ok
I forgot something the second way to
stop your bad emotion
just just don't be near your
husband you're stupid oh wait a minute I'll be right back
avoid him and go somewhere
outside wait 10 minutes
come back my dear I thought you were
stupid
good still curled up and again
different things for an hour for half an hour right you will
come back darling I thought you were stupid
let's all get ahead to mom life a
couple of days more avoid this he
passed avoid this the second way
to stop negative emotions this is not
real  Buddhism is not real
real Buddhism
use the understanding of emptiness
use the understanding of emptiness but if you are not
strong enough and just avoid it will
help those people who bring you
problems avoid
if your husband is yelling and the children are angry in the cafeteria
this is Buddhism it will not change your problems
but it will make you stronger it will calm
you down and it will help you it is good
if someone brings problems to your life a
small little antidote
just avoid be calm
but it will not fix your problem there
will be a problem the goal of Buddhism mom
fix the problem forever did it interfere does
this mean if my husband is going to
merge now I should not go to
another room I did not say this it is
normal but it will not stop the problem it will
just be a little at Astana
it is a good thing to do but it will not
stop your problem forever it will
not fix the goal of Buddhism
to stop the problem forever it is clear for
today's evening we have enough do not
forget especially and the blessing of
emptiness
you will be another man today okay it is
normal it is normal okay don't
be surprised okay don't
be surprised outside your house
I have outside my house at  I have
an anthill, they do some kind of work there,
I don't bother them, they
bother me, these big red ants, you
know, they can bite you, but we
have an agreement,
they don't bother me, and I don't step on them,
so sometimes I accidentally
just step on them,
and they bite me, you see, what else am I
saying to you? Your consciousness, your
consciousness, you are now in your consciousness,
and your consciousness, sometimes you will get angry,
and that's normal, but when you
study Buddhism, my story to your ear,
when you study knowledge according to the article, you
just boil it down there, stronger today,
tomorrow,
you will get even more angry, but that's a
good sign, you understand,
you need to stew in this a little,
and then you will kill your bad ones,
if you don't get upset,
don't get angry, if you get angry, borscht
tonight or tomorrow, that's a good
sign, good, it comes out, bad things
come out,
my teacher said, if today you
heard two husbands in the kitchen, and you go to
bed, and you sleep, and in a dream, Bilan joins, and
You start vomiting, then you don't
see yourself. This is a good dream. This means
bad things are coming out of you. Debts, bad
karma. You'll stop yourself. So don't be upset.
If you get upset,
just relax. When you
really start studying the emptiness,
all the bad seeds begin to grow,
awaken, and come out of you. They
die, and according to the article, and be a business. People
who really understand the post, you
could, in a few days they
will get even more problem points. Understanding,
more and more emptiness, even more,
selects these bad seeds from you, and they
end. You understand, so don't
belittle this. You will be
upset. This is normal, but we are
killing italki.
We are cleansing. This is clear. Thank you, thank you,
everyone. Moms, on paper, a mandala.
They forgot the mandala, and this will be
Yolanda. Read the mandala. She is the director, the
operating director, at the retreat. In appearance,
this is pain. She has a lot of work.
Seba, she has a huge thank you for everything. Let's go on the
road, a little rifle,
running,
pancakes, and
sleds.
Action. Mitya
and the Gulag. And only
we have Torshina,
this one, and
Aksha, and there.  spring mandala
somnia and I do
n't drink beer it's like
and I still have to
learn the sunnah
yet
no one would
there perch that
from the show
[music]
thank you very much something
else